mega.com 2018-10-19

# Privacy Policy | Enterprise Architecture Software for Digital Transformation | MEGA

MEGA appreciates your visit to our Web site and thanks you for your interest in our company, products, and services. Your privacy is important to MEGA, so we created a policy that explains how we collect, use, share, and store your information. This policy discloses the information practices for all MEGA Web sites.

## Collection of personal information - Cookies

### What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a person’s computer as they navigate through different websites. The collection of cookies helps us understand how our website is being used, user behavior, and also tells us which parts of our website have been visited. It enables us to also tailor messages and display ads to a given person’s interests on our website and on other platforms. Cookie collection facilitates and measures the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. Cookies are stored for 13 months, unless the person decides to delete them before the end of that term.

At MEGA, we treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

### Which cookies do we use and to what end?

We only use tracking cookies on our website. They are then used for marketing and commercial purposes.

  1. Cookies needing your consent  

    1. Pardot  
Pardot cookies are tracking cookies attached to the forms on our websites and to our tracking links. Collected data includes: information about your visits and use of all MEGA websites, as well as information that you provide for the purpose of registering to our events and/or subscribing to our communications and resources.  
Personal data that you submit on the forms (such as your name, email, company, etc.) may be used to improve your browsing experience and send information to you by email.
    2. Google Analytics  
Google analytics uses cookies to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior in an anonymous form. All information is processed to compile statistical reports on MEGA’s website activities. Google analytics cookies help us to optimize your navigation and improve content. The use of those cookies does not allow us to identify you personally, and cannot be used from one website to another.
  2. Cookies not needing your consent  
We also use session cookies, which are temporary files to identify and track users when navigating our website. Those cookies are deleted when you leave our website.

### How to configure your browser

  1. Google Chrome  

    1. Go to the menu on the toolbar.
    2. Select “Settings”.
    3. Click on “Advanced settings”.
    4. In the “Privacy” section, click on “Content settings” to select your configuration.
  2. Internet Explorer  

    1. Click on “Tools”, then on “Internet options”.
    2. Navigate to the “Privacy” section, then the “Settings” section
    3. Select your configuration.
    4. Click “Ok” on the bottom to confirm your choice.
  3. Mozilla Firefox  

    1. Go to the “Tools” section and click on “Options”.
    2. Go to the “Privacy” section.
    3. Choose your configuration and click on “Ok” to confirm.
  4. Apple Safari (Windows, Mac OS)  

    1. In the toolbar, choose “Preferences”.
    2. Go to the “Privacy” section.
    3. Choose your configuration and close the window to confirm  

## Use of personal information

Here are the main examples of how we may use your personal information:

### Fulfilling your request

If you request something from MEGA, such as a product or service, a callback, marketing materials, or specific information, we use the information you provide to fulfill your request and personalizing the interaction with you.

The personal information you provide MEGA, as well as the information we can collect about you indirectly, may be used for marketing purposes, which may keep you informed about on MEGA’s latest publications, corporate information, product and services announcements, upcoming events, or other types of information that may interest you. You may at any time choose not to receive marketing materials from us by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each email you may receive, by indicating so when we call you, or by contacting us directly.

### Providing Support

We may use your personal information to support products or services you have obtained from us, such as notifying you of a product update or change. In any case, MEGA will use your personal information in an effort to provide you with the highest quality services, personalized in accordance with your wishes.

### Sharing of personal information

As an international organization, the personal information we collect may be transferred throughout MEGA’s worldwide organization and certified partner distributor network. We will not sell your personal information or share it with any other third party. Each time you provide us with your personal information, you are notified about the reason, whether it is to download information, inquire about a product, register for a Webinar, or any other purpose. It is completely up to you whether you want to provide personal information.

### Access to your personal information

At any time, you are entitled to know whether we hold personal information about you and, if we do, to have access to it and be able to corrected it if it is inaccurate.  
Moreover, you are entitled to revoke your consent to our use of your personal information in the future, in whole or in part. Should you desire this, we will delete or store your data. You can do this by sending us an [email](mailto:info@mega.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Information).  
MEGA will make every effort to ensure the protection of your personal information on our servers, and will respond to any suspected abuse that you report to us.

If you have any further questions about our privacy policy, [please contact us](mailto:info@mega.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Information).  
MEGA may update his privacy policy from time to time. When we update the policy, a notice will be posted on our web site.

 _Last updated: June 8, 2016_
